<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>A Home for Mo</title>
        <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/</link>
        <description>My name is Mo and we&#39;re making me a new home!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:19:34 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Welcome</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/welcome/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:19:34 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
                    <name>Mo</name>
                </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/welcome/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/Welcome.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Thanks so much for visiting my website! I cannot talk or communicate, so my dad made this website for me, to tell my story.
Love, Mo <i class="fa fa-heart"></i>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Friday 11 February 2022</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2022-02-11/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2022-02-11/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The last couple of months have been stressful on multiple fronts, but this week we had the news we&rsquo;ve been waiting for. Contracts exchanged - and the new house becomes ours NEXT MONDAY! Valentine&rsquo;s Day! (We&rsquo;re in love. <i class="fas fa-grin-hearts"></i>)
Over the next five weeks, there&rsquo;s a lot of work to coordinate - electrical, plastering, hoist installation, wheelchair-accessible doors, some decorating and so on. This is all to make the property ready for us to move into at the end of March.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Saturday, 18 December 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-12-18/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-12-18/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A lot has happened since our last update - including the whole family catching COVID. We put our house on the market in September and agreed a sale in about a week. After that, the pressure was on to find the new home.
With very little on the market, even less that was suitable, we placed an offer, which was then accepted, on a lovely house in Mickle Trafford, a village just outside Chester.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Wednesday, 1 September 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-09-01/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-09-01/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/AHFM-Missions-2021-09-01.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>It&rsquo;s getting real.
Almost all the work on our current home is finished. New hall, stairs and landing carpet to be fitted shortly. Existing home goes on the market in a fortnight. We viewed two potential new homes yesterday - one is a very strong contender. The strong contender involves some compromise - mainly that it has a very small garden. But the layout is the best we&rsquo;ve seen so far (although some structural work will still be needed).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Monday, 2 August 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-08-02/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-08-02/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/2021-08-01_SundayTimes-crop.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Good news, hot off the press - in more ways than one.
You may have seen our story in the Sunday Times at the weekend. To our utter astonishment, it was the lead story in the Money section. The journalist Imogen Tew did a great job, covering the issue we referred to in our last update: that mortgage lenders would not permit us to apply any of the funds raised towards a deposit on a purchase.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Thursday, 15 July 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-07-15/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-07-15/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[We made an interesting &amp; slightly awkward discovery in the last fortnight. Due to increasing regulation in the finance sector, residential lenders make more queries than ever about the source of funds for a deposit. It turns out they will not accept funds raised through campaigns like this!
We had previously believed that any spare funds raised (beyond what’s needed for adaptations) could “extend our reach”, to slightly more expensive properties.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Tuesday, 29 June 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-06-29/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-06-29/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/AHFM-Missions-2021-06-29.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Hi!
We&rsquo;re probably overdue an update. In today&rsquo;s update, we&rsquo;ll focus on our missions.
Mission 1: find the funds Mission 2: ready to sell Mission 3: find the house Mission 4: ready to move Thank you once more to everyone who is so generously helping us with mission 1 (find the funds). The fundraising stands at nearly £75,000, which is awesome.
Over the last few weeks, we&rsquo;ve been beavering away at mission 2 (get ready to sell).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Wednesday, 19 May 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-19/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-19/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Today promises to be quite an exciting day! We&rsquo;re already off to a storming start, with a lovely article in our local news outlet:
And we&rsquo;re bracing ourselves, Sharon and I, for an interview at 10:30am today on our local radio station, Dee 106.3. You can listen online here. Check timing in your local time zone.
Please do consider continuing to share our website and fundraising page with your contacts near and far.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Thursday, 13 May 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-13/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-13/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sharon and I had a great (nerve-wracking) opportunity to speak live on UCB2 this morning about special needs parenting and the ongoing campaign to raise money towards a home for Morgan.
This interview focuses a lot on our faith and how it affects our story. If that&rsquo;s not your jam, we understand, no problem. <i class="fa fa-heart"></i>
Thank you UCB and to all those who made this happen! We have some further possible opportunities to tell our story in the media - we&rsquo;ll let you know if they come to fruition.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Friday, 7 May 2021</title>
    <link>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-07/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 17:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><author>
        <name>Rob Pomeroy</name>
    </author><guid>http://ahfm.pomeroy.me/2021-05-07/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/thank-you.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>We launched the fundraising campaign yesterday, not at all knowing what to expect. We had set the target at £15,000, and that felt audacious. As I posted the links to social media, I was thinking something I&rsquo;ve said to a few friends recently, as we discussed this idea: &ldquo;Nothing ventured, nothing gained.&rdquo;
What did I think would happen? I wasn&rsquo;t sure, but in my heart of hearts, I thought maybe we&rsquo;d raise a few thousand pounds, and that would be amazing.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
