<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on A Home for Mo</title>
    <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on A Home for Mo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:15:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ahomeformo.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A New Home</title>
      <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/new-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:15:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/new-home/</guid>
      <description>I live with my family in Chester, England. As I&amp;rsquo;ve grown older, and needed more and more help, our previous house became too small for me. Soon I will have two carers with me, round the clock. I needed more space for my supplies, my equipment and my carers. And it&amp;rsquo;s important to keep my family together. So my mum and dad have been working hard to find us a new home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Campaign</title>
      <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:15:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/campaign/</guid>
      <description>When my mum and dad worked out how much it would cost to get a new home ready for me, they realised they couldn&amp;rsquo;t do it alone. They didn&amp;rsquo;t like to ask for help, but friends insisted they should. So, thinking maybe we would raise one or two thousand pounds, my dad set up a GoFundMe page.
Widget can&#39;t display. Please visit GoFundMe. It is impossible to put into words how astonished and grateful we all were as the donations poured in, in the end raising over £100,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello!My identical twin James and I :(fa fa-male): :(fa fa-male): were born in 2004, 10 weeks early. We are survivors of twin-to-twin transfusion syndrome. Because of this condition, I am profoundly disabled :(fa fa-wheelchair-alt):, quadriplegic with severe spastic cerebral palsy, epilepsy and profound learning difficulties. We live with our Mum &amp;amp; Dad in Chester in the UK.
Highs :(fa fa-thumbs-up): and Lows :(fa fa-thumbs-down):Like many people, I have a mixed life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/faqs/</guid>
      <description>James on the left, Morgan on the right: incubator transport
Q: What were you looking for in the new home?
A: As with any house purchase, some things were non-negotiable and others were nice-to-have! The non-negotiables:
Privacy*. This essentially meant a separate &amp;ldquo;wing&amp;rdquo; or annex for Mo, where sound doesn&amp;rsquo;t travel too much into the main house. Morgan can be quite noisy, at any time of the day! This also means that he can enjoy things like music therapy without worrying about the impact on anyone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahomeformo.com/pages/media/</guid>
      <description>Campaign videoThis is the video my dad made, to launch the fundraising campaign.
Media appearancesI&amp;rsquo;ve been in the media a bit - find out more below!
National and Local News Sunday Times (paywall)
Chester Standard
Cheshire Live
National and Local Radio Premier Radio
Premier Radio interview page Dee 106.3 Radio
UBC Radio</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
